dumex.com.cn 2002-12-04

# YoungNutrition.net

INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD gathers two types of information about users: data that users provide through optional, voluntary registrations on several of our sites and in certain contests and sweepstakes; and data INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD gathers through aggregating tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites and click through on our newsletters. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and help us better understand the demographics of our audience in order to better service them online.  

INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD gathers user information in the following processes:   

*** Optional registration**   
Several INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD sites offer free, voluntary registration to users. By registering, users can enter the sites without having to log on each time; they gain access to the polling area; they can enter chatrooms and message boards; and they can take advantage of personalization (the ability to select content according to a user-supplied profile).   
During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address, and may have to answer various survey questions about age, gender, income, Internet connection, zip code, country, employment status, and other related information.   
During registration the user has the option of supplying a first name, last name, and password hint. In addition, the user can opt to subscribe to various INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD electronic newsletters and to have his or her email address and/or URL appear in postings.   

*** Polling**   
Several INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD sites offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what the INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD audience thinks about important issues. INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD uses a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.   

*** Message boards/forums**   
Users of the INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD Message Boards must register for this service (free of charge) in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address.   

*** Electronic newsletters (Dispatches)**   
INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD sites may offer a free electronic newsletter to users. INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list through the subscription management pages or by sending an e-mail message to the appropriate address listed in the newsletter. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.   
INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD delivers newsletters, marketing and product offerings via email to only registered recipients from our subscription center. The email tracking system recognizes the URL that was clicked, and records some information about you and your computer, such as the email address that you provided to us, the browser, operating system and IP address.   
INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD also uses the feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your system. This allows us to measure and report the click through rate on e-mails delivered and them better determine future content.   
INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD will not provide specific user information to any third party company.   

*** "Send this story to a friend" service**   
On some of INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD sites, a reader can choose to electronically forward a story or article to someone else by clicking the link at the top of that story. The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the story. The information is not used for any other purpose.   

*** Surveys**   
Occasionally INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.   

*** Contests and sweepstakes**   
INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD offers contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information. At a minimum, the required information includes name and email address; in some cases, the user must answer mandatory survey questions about a range of other personal data. The information gathered in the entry form is used to verify the entrant's identity, to send the entrant an email notification that their entry has been received, and to contact winners and/or prize recipients. There are two situations in which INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD will divulge this information to a third party--provided the user gives express consent: 

**(1)** A user may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest sponsor, in which case the user's personally identifiable information is divulged to the advertiser. 

**(2)** Some of the contests may be hosted on the INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD site but administered by the sponsor; in such cases, the information a user provides is passed on to the third party as long as that user gives express consent. 

Because the rules and terms of each contest can vary, all information about each contest is clearly posted during the event. All contests and sweepstakes are conducted in full accordance with local laws. 

*** Usage tracking**   
INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites.   

*** Cookies**   
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above), when you register as a INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD member, and when you click an ad:   

  | **Registration:** when you register, INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. Cookies also enable you to enter INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD sites as a member without having to log on each time, and to visit member-restricted areas of the sites. We encrypt the user ID for added security.  |   
---|---|---  
  
If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie.   
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COMPANY PTE LTD Message Boards.
